TREVOR JOHNSON

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

- **8**12-545-0552
- ✓ tJohnsonAce@outlook.com
- Indiana, USA
- trevorjohnson.vercel.app

SKILLS

- · Web Design
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- React.js
- Next.js
- Tailwind

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S OF SCIENCE

Vincennes University 2013 - 2017

COURSERA

Meta Front-End Course 2022

PROFILE

I discovered the magic of code and quickly fell in love with front-end development. The ability to write code and watch it transform into responsive and creative designs never ceases to amaze me. My core expertise lies in working with HTML, CSS, JS, React, Nextjs, and Tailwind, but I pride myself on being adaptable and can quickly grasp new technologies. Committed to continuous growth, I strive to learn something new every single day and look forward to a bright future in the ever-evolving world of tech.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

3MetaD

Feb 2023 - Present

- Implemented strategic changes and leveraged Google Analytics to optimize the user experience, resulting in a 21% increase in overall
- Spearheaded efforts to attract new users, leading to a significant 28% boost in new user engagement.
- Effectively reduced bounce rate by 38%, creating a more engaging and interactive site, retaining users for longer periods.
- Successfully increased the event count by 7%, by enhancing the site's functionality and responsiveness.

SURVEILLANCE SUPERVISOR

French Lick Casino

2017 - Present

- Developed and implemented comprehensive training programs for surveillance personnel
- Identified and reported instances of cheating and advantage play to management
- Conducted regular audits of surveillance footage to ensure compliance with established protocols
- Scheduled and managed surveillance shifts to ensure adequate coverage of all areas of the casino